# MARKO MILICIC

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### **CONTACTS**



hello@markomilicic.com



+41 79 829 9681



@mmarkomilicic



markomilicic.com

#### **SKILLS**

#### **LANGUAGES**

Java, C# [ASP.NET, .NET Core], SQL [Oracle, MySQL, SQL Server], Python, Rust, Solidity

#### FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

Django, Spring Boot, Vaadin, Selenium

#### OTHER

Git, AWS, Blockchain, Enterprise Architect, Visual Studio Code, Photoshop

## **LANGUAGES**

ITALIAN | Mother tongue

**SERBIAN** | Mother tongue

ENGLISH | Professional - B2.2 Certicate

SPANISH | Professional

#### **ABOUT**

I'm a passionate Full Stack developer with expertise in in various programming languages and frameworks. I have a strong grasp of cloud technologies, particularly AWS, for deploying and scaling applications.

I'm enthusiastic about the tech community and always open to new challenges and opportunities for growth in software development

## **EXPERIENCE**

Good Code | Full Stack Developer

Manno, Switzerland, november 2022 - present

I'm Specialize in developing customized management software solutions for our clients using mainly Java Spring Boot, Vaadin and MySQL, also involved in web scraping projects, using Python and tools such as Selenium to automate online processes, and much more.

Red Cross Ticino | Stage - Full Stack Developer

Lugano, Switzerland, august 2021 - april 2022

I worked on the development of a prototype management software designed to simplify member and donor management. The project began with a detailed needs analysis. I used Python and the Django framework for the backend, integrated MySQL for database management, and implemented Bootstrap for the frontend.

### **EDUCATION**

**SUPSI** | Certificate of Advanced Studies in Blockchain

Lugano, Switzerland november 2022 - july 2023

Franklyn University | PLANB Summer School, Blockchain

Lugano, Switzerland, 2022

**SSSE** | Bachelor in Business Informatics

Bellinzona, Switzerland, september 2019 - june 2022